What is Liang Hong doing?
Can't she prioritize?
Such a huge change...
Why wasn't it reported beforehand?
Sir.
Staff Officer Liang went with the squad to scout the enemy.
She did report it in advance.
Why didn't she keep a close eye on Guo Zijian?
Guo Zijian is the Red Force's main offensive force.
He is the biggest variable.
He certainly is a variable.
With this move of his,
he almost took out the Blue Force Command Post.
Find out immediately
if Guo Zijian carried out
a precision strike on the Blue Force Command Post
because he received orders from the Red Force Command Post,
or if he personally
obtained some key information.
Sir, but...
This is a back-to-back exercise.
Whatever tactics they use,
how could they possibly report everything to us?
Don't contradict me.
The hills in this exercise are fixed.
The number of troops is fixed.
Their numbers, their strengths and weaknesses,
I am fully aware of them all.
Right, right, right.
Even if a stone on the battlefield shifted,
you would be fully aware.
Report.
What's the situation with Liang Hong?
Liang Hong's team
followed the 396th Brigade 1st Battalion's recon squad
and discovered the Blue Force Command Post.
Understood.
Hurry up and contact the exercise controller team,
and have them report updates constantly.
Yes, Sir.
Did you hear that?
That's the catch here.
Someone like Staff Officer Liang,
who can always grasp the core of any matter,
is the best Exercise Controller.
Xu Lingjun.
You really...
are getting better at Making snide remarks.
Am I?
The results are out.
Report.
Speak.
Exercise Control ruled
our 1st Battalion's strike on the Blue Force command center was effective,
causing the Blue Force command center
to lose 60% of its combat capability.
Beautiful!
Good!
Great!
Wow, nicely done!
60% of their forces damaged...
That means Long Yuanshan escaped.
Our two recon teams might have been captured.
That's a shame.
But right at the start,
Guo Zijian managed to take out
60% of the Black Mamba command headquarters.
That's not bad at all.
Don't celebrate just yet.
Long Yuanshan is an old fox.
A crazy old fox.
Taking a bite out of him won't be easy.
Regardless,
in Long Yuanshan's history of exercises,
this must be a first.
Political Commissar, where are you going?
I've been holding it in. To the restroom.
It was just a fluke.
Faults should be punished, merits rewarded.
Long Yuanshan's forces are damaged,
and his position is exposed.
His original battle plan has been ruined.
If my guess is right,
he'll rendezvous with the troops at Jade Emperor Peak
for a showdown with us.
Are the 3rd and 4th Battalions in position?
They're almost at Shigun River.
Order them
to speed up and secure Jade Emperor Peak.
Yes, sir.
Order
the 1st and 2nd Battalions
to stand by and stay on high alert.
Yes, sir.
To shift the strike target this quickly
from West Wind Valley to Second Slope,
they must have prepared a Plan B.
It seems the Red Force recon team didn't just stumble in.
They came straight for our command center.
The Red Force must have an expert among them.
When the first recon squad came over,
I should've adjusted our combat deployment immediately.
I wasn't vigilant enough.
I was a bit too arrogant.
We underestimated Suo Jian'an.
But since they already knew
the coordinates of our command post,
why did they only send one battalion's firepower
to strike us?
If they had concentrated their main forces here,
we'd very likely have been completely wiped out.
Here's the info the scouts just sent.
Look at the Red Army main force's current deployment.
They're massing at Jade Emperor Peak.
It seems Suo Jian'an wants
to commit to the battle at Jade Emperor Peak
and draw us out into the open.
In that case,
this surprise attack
wasn't ordered by Suo Jian'an.
Furthermore, Suo Jian'an
might not fully trust this person's judgment.
That's why he chose this
strategy he considered safe.
Could this just be a battalion commander's spur-of-the-moment idea?
You can tell
it's a main assault battalion,
and its attached firepower is decent.
But its authority is limited, after all.
They can't command deeper strike forces.
That's why we managed to escape.
What do you think?
Since they want to draw us to Jade Emperor Peak
for a decisive battle,
then let's grant his wish.
Reinforce Jade Emperor Peak.
Hit them hard.
The more brutal the battle, the better.
In that case, it'll just be a war of attrition.
Sometimes attrition creates tactical opportunities.
Since we're launching a Feint attack,
we might as well make it convincing.
Captain, do we engage?
Engage? How can we fight that?
But the Battalion Commander...
Didn't he tell us to clear out enemy remnants?
Can you use your brain for a second?
Does that look like remnants?
That's at least the strength of a Combined Arms Battalion.
We aren't scared. Let's take them on.
Take them on? No way.
This battle has just begun.
It's not your time to die a hero yet.
Tell the men to let them pass.
And send two scouts...
...to see where exactly they're going.
Yes, sir.
After all that intense bombing...
...they still aren't crippled.
Jade Emperor Peak. Every year, it's Jade Emperor Peak.
What kind of game is Long Yuanshan playing here?
Is he really going to fight Red Force at Jade Emperor Peak...
...to the bitter end?
Someone else might fight like that,
...but not Long Yuanshan.
He's a sly old fox.
If he's going to Jade Emperor Peak...
...he must have another motive.
So you're saying...
...Red Force is fighting just to fight,
...while Blue Force is fighting to adapt?
Xu Lingjun,
...your understanding has improved.
If it were out of ten points,
I'd give you a seven.
I passed again. Thank you, Sir.
What's the status of the maneuver?
Attention!
Sit.
According to your orders,
...we flanked directly back from Yellow Stone Ridge.
After Second Slope was suppressed by heavy fire,
...we encountered basically no resistance.
However,
we ran into...
...Long Yuanshan's main force while they were relocating.
How many casualties did you take?
None, actually.
I figured that our sharp sword...
...would be put to great use later on.
So we avoided close-quarters combat.
However,
I sent two scouts to follow them,
...hoping to locate their backup command post.
Not bad. You've learned to use your brain.
I learned it all from you.
Has Wu Dongsheng returned yet?
He got their core coordinates,
...so they've likely all been taken prisoner.
We'll celebrate their achievement after the battle.
That's great.
What's our next mission?
Stand by and stay on high alert.
Are they treating our main assault battalion like reserves?
I was still planning to go up Jade Emperor Peak...
...and hit these Black Mambas hard.
Li Songwei!
Here!
The unit I used against the Second Battalion earlier,
...a Battalion Combat Group, is assigned to you.
You will move on my orders at any time.
Also,
whatever happens with those two scouts,
report to me immediately.
Yes, sir.
Why do I have a bad feeling about this?
Are you going to ignore orders...
...and go rogue on your own?
Don't put that label on me.
When have I ever ignored orders?
I'm just adapting to a special situation.
Besides,
I've already reported my actions to the brigade commanders.
Alright, you guys get some rest.
Wait for my orders.
Yes, sir.
Long Yuanshan is throwing a combo at us.
Sir, an accident occurred during the exercise.
We need your orders.
What kind of accident?
Wu Dongsheng, 1st Battalion Recon Squad Leader, 396th Brigade,
while carrying out a reconnaissance mission,
was severely injured in a vehicle accident.
What's his condition?
Right now, our Exercise Controllers
have already taken him to the field hospital.
He is undergoing a comprehensive examination.
Initial assessment indicates severe leg trauma,
and he is currently unconscious.
Don't send him to the field hospital.
Pass on my orders.
Dispatch a transport helicopter to send him to
the 189th Hospital, closest to the exercise area.
Notify the hospital
to assemble their best experts to stand by for treatment.
Yes, sir.
The ones who arranged for him to go to the field hospital
were Liang Hong's team.
Yes.
Good.
She did well.
She didn't panic because of the sudden emergency,
nor did she shirk responsibility due to her other tasks.
Of course.
Liang Hong is your top student, personally trained by you.
But as for Liang Hong and her team's next tasks,
what's the plan?
What do you mean, what's the plan?
She will continue executing her exercise control tasks.
Inform her and all other exercise participants
that this news must be kept strictly confidential.
All issues will be dealt with after the exercise
has concluded.
Yes, sir.
Reporting, Sir.
What's the situation?
We are facing fierce resistance at Jade Emperor Peak.
Judging from their firepower,
the enemy has far more than just one battalion.
Good.
Just as I expected.
Long Yuanshan came after all.
Order
the 2nd Battalion to set out immediately.
With the support of the 3rd and 4th Battalions,
launch a full assault on the main peak of Jade Emperor Peak.
Strike directly at the enemy's heart.
Furthermore,
the 1st Battalion will stay on the perimeter of Jade Emperor Peak
to provide support.
Yes, Sir!
Jian'an,
if we mass all our forces
and assemble them at Jade Emperor Peak,
isn't it too risky?
It's already quite obvious now.
Jade Emperor Peak has become a focal point of this Red-Blue confrontation.
We currently have the numerical advantage.
We must seize the opportunity to capture it.
Otherwise, we'll miss the window of opportunity.
But I can't help feeling that this tactic
isn't Long Yuanshan's style.
I actually think
we forced his hand.
He has no other choice.
Let's push a little harder.
Victory is in sight.
This afternoon,
the combat troops at Jade Emperor Peak
will carry out two forced assaults.
The time interval between them can be kept
to under two hours.
This will pin down the Red Army's heavy armor forces
and create a siphon effect,
luring the Red Army into continuously deploying
follow-up combat forces to Jade Emperor Peak.
Yes, Sir!
The engineer demolition detachment
will wait for the Red Army's heavy armor forces
to reinforce the Shigun River line.
On their advance route,
they will conduct indiscriminate demolitions to halt them.
Then, laser systems will guide long-range firepower
to conduct precision strikes on the targets.
Yes, Sir!
The 4th Heavy Battalion's anti-armor detachment
will feign an aggressive push toward the Red Army's command post,
forcing their nearby main forces
to launch a full-scale counterattack.
Yes, Sir!
The heliborne detachment will seize the chaos for a decapitation strike,
aiming to complete a lightning raid
on the Red Army's command post in the shortest time possible,
and capture Suo Jian'an alive.
Yes, Sir!
The signal corps,
once the heliborne detachment moves out,
will target all communication bands of the Red Army
to conduct full-network and full-frequency Jamming,
coordinating with the decapitation strike.
Yes, Sir!
Move out.
Yes, Sir.
The 1st Battalion is clearly the main assault unit.
Why are we relegated to perimeter support?
Enough, obey orders!
Assemble the troops.
Yes, Sir.
Wait.
Guo Zijian,
in that head of yours,
are you scheming something again?
Something's wrong.
Signalman!
Here, Sir!
Connect me to the command post.
Yes, Sir!
Reporting, Battalion Commander. You're connected.
This is Guo Zijian, 1st Battalion Commander.
You'd better just worry about yourself.
Ridiculous.
You think you're a big shot.
Staff Officer Liang,
please make sure
you edit this part out for us.
This has nothing to do with the exercise.
Who were you complaining about?
Who else? Guo Zijian.
What happened?
He suggested the main forces immediately pull out tonight
from the attack on Jade Emperor Peak.
Can't you change your bad temper?
Can't we just talk things out?
Dealing with Liu Xinyan,
even a hundred good tempers wouldn't be enough.
But no matter what,
we shouldn't have suggested
that the main force
withdraw from the main battlefield tonight.
That's not something a battalion commander should suggest.
Political Instructor.
This Long Yuanshan is craftier than a ghost in battle.
When have you ever seen him
fight a hard war of attrition head-on?
He acted completely out of character at Jade Emperor Peak.
And that was after his main force took heavy losses from us,
and he didn't have the numerical advantage.
Let me tell you,
there must be a conspiracy here.
Then what exactly
is his trick?
We can't always rely on intuition
to fight battles, can we?
As a commander,
you can't always rely on intuition
to direct a battle.
Alright, I haven't figured it out yet.
Then take your time to figure it out.
Before we figure it out,
we just need to do one thing.
Obey orders.
Any news from Li Songwei's scouts?
No.
We have confirmed
that the Red team's command post is at Wild Fox Ridge.
We can execute the decapitation strike at any time.
Brigade Commander.
Caught two tails.
Scouts again.
Wave after wave, it's endless.
Seems they really won't let go.
Whose soldiers are you two?
Still acting all tough, huh?
Interesting.
I'm getting more and more curious.
Here's the plan.
The PLA always treats prisoners well.
Tell the mess squad
to give these two and those five red-billed birds
an extra dish of fried pork.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Notify the command post at Tiger's Mouth.
All electronic warfare and jamming equipment,
turn them all on.
Maximize the power.
Yes, sir.
Old Long.
Aren't you afraid of exposing the command post's location?
If he can really find this place based on that,
I'll admit he's capable.
Besides, I want to see
the one who stirred up the hornet's nest against me, Long Yuanshan,
and find out exactly who they are.
I think you're
thinking of Poaching again.
Report.
Speak.
The Blue team is heavily surrounded by us,
and they are attempting to break out.
The command center ordered us to advance quickly
and eliminate them.
Break out?
There must be The catch.
Has the brigade command post followed up?
No follow-up notification yet.
Get me the Second Battalion Commander.
Yes, sir.
201, 201.
10113, 10113.
Report.
Speak.
Commander, call from First Battalion Commander Guo Zijian.
Jiang Shengqiang.
I know you have a problem with me,
but now is not the time to butt heads.
I'm not asking you to disobey orders either.
Do you see the Shigun River?
The terrain there is narrow,
and heavy equipment passes slowly.
It will take a longer time.
If the enemy strikes us there,
our forces will likely be cut off.
Do you know why Long Yuanshan is fighting like this?
So I suspect...
I know what you're suspecting.
Guo Zijian.
I know how to fight the Second Battalion's battle.
Mind your own business.
How come you're not angry anymore?
Does getting angry help?
How can a commander lose his temper?
I've made my point.
How much he understands is up to him.
Since we can't control others,
we just have to rely on ourselves.
We're moving out soon.
Where are you going?
You go on ahead.
I'm heading to the electronic warfare unit.
Everyone, listen to my orders!
Move out!
Yes, sir!
Order Second Battalion to halt their advance.
Have them reinforce our command center
to prevent a Blue Force decapitation strike.
Deploy heavy equipment decoys
near the Shigun River front to confuse the enemy.
And keep an anti-aircraft unit in reserve.
Isn't this disobeying orders?
Cut the crap.
I'll report it to the brigade commander.
Notify Xu Dali.
Tell him to guard the northeast side of the brigade command post.
He is not to leave without orders.
Yes, sir!
This time, Long Yuanshan
seems to...
Sir! Sir!
Look.
Long Yuanshan has launched his combo attacks.
The show has begun.
Report.
Speak.
The Shigun River assembly area for heavy armored forces
was hit by the Blue Force's long-range fire.
The losses are severe.
Understood.
Yes, sir.
The more Long Yuanshan risks his life like this,
the more it proves there's an issue with Jade Emperor Peak.
Chief of Staff.
Here.
Quickly organize an evacuation,
regroup personnel and equipment,
and continue completing the encirclement of Jade Emperor Peak.
This is an order,
not a discussion.
Yes, sir.
Report.
Come in.
Blue Force vehicles and personnel were spotted in the Shigun River direction.
Using laser guidance,
they are targeting our heavy armored forces
by executing pinpoint precision strikes.
Due to destroyed equipment blocking the way,
the follow-up forces can't advance further.
What the hell are the security forces doing?
Where are they?
There are gaps between the battalions responsible for security.
I think the Blue Force used these gaps
to infiltrate.
Notify the recon battalion
to drive them away.
Yes, sir.
Hurry up!
Report from the Shigun River direction!
The Exercise Control Center informed us
that after the Blue Force's long-range artillery strike,
their infantry anti-armor forces
have occupied the main passages.
At the same time, their engineers
blew up and destroyed the various passages.
They have already split our forces.
That's so weird.
These Blue Force units...
how did they appear in our combat zone so quickly?
Where did they pop out from?
Order!
Yes, sir.
All 1st and 2nd Battalion personnel near the command post,
retreat immediately!
Yes, sir.
Report.
Speak.
Since the Blue Force launched their long-range strike,
they started targeting all our communication methods
with full-band Jamming.
We can't communicate.
Change channels and keep trying to contact them
until we get through.
Yes, sir.
What is Long Yuanshan trying to do?
The battle has barely just started!
He wants a decapitation strike.
The support troops don't have heavy equipment.
We must be on guard.
The Blue Force's intense Jamming is very formidable.
We're currently conducting anti-jamming against them.
Can we use the Jamming signal
to determine where the Blue Force command post is?
Theoretically, it's possible.
But we currently don't have the capability
to perform such complex calculations.
Don't we have
a great Doctor of Information Engineering here?
But she's an Exercise Controller.
Wouldn't it be a violation for her to help us?
Who asked her to help?
I'll just give her a problem to test her.
It's a purely professional exchange.
I came to see you about a personal matter.
Can we turn this thing off first?
Battalion Commander Guo,
we are currently in an exercise.
All right.
I just thought
that after the exercise is over,
I'd treat you to dinner.
Just the two of us.
What?
Are you trying to pursue me?
The book says
inviting a familiar friend of the opposite sex to dinner
means you are pursuing them.
I wouldn't dare. I wouldn't dare.
I just want to have a simple academic exchange with you.
That's good.
Do you really look down on me that much?
Anything goes as friends,
but if we were to be partners,
at least in terms of knowledge and IQ,
we need to be on the same level.
What does that mean?
You, a Doctor, look down on a Master's grad like me?
I didn't say that. You said it yourself.
Fine.
But now I think
getting a doctorate isn't that hard.
Besides, Deputy Army Commander Liang is your mentor.
It'd be easy for him to pull some strings for you.
My doctorate
was earned through my own abilities.
Even though Deputy Army Commander Liang is my mentor,
but my doctorate
was earned point by point on my own exams.
It's entirely based on my own abilities,
and has nothing to do with fraud.
Don't get worked up.
How about this?
Recently,
I came across a problem in a book.
I've been stuck on it for days.
If you can solve it for me,
I will admit
that your degree
is the real deal.
Ridiculous.
My degree
is certified by the academy.
I don't need your approval at all.
If you can't solve it, just say so.
No need for pretty excuses.
What problem?
Reporting!
Report.
Jiang Shengqiang, Commander of the 2nd Battalion,
is reporting via landline.
Deputy Chief of Staff Li
has been declared killed in action at the front line.
The 2nd Battalion has rallied the 3rd and 4th Battalions.
We're using current forces to block the Blue Army's division tactics,
and seeking to counter-encircle them.
Good.
Tell Jiang Shengqiang...
tell him I said...
he did a beautiful job.
Yes, sir!
Also,
tell him
the Blue Army's command center
has been severely crippled by Guo Zijian.
They've suffered heavy losses
and are already a spent force.
Tell him to hit them hard, give them no quarter!
Yes, sir!
Good old Jiang Shengqiang.
He really stepped up at the critical moment.
That's why I say, Political Commissar,
stop fixating on Guo Zijian.
Our brigade is full of talent.
Honestly,
in my eyes,
even two Guo Zijians
might not match up to one Jiang Shengqiang.
If Jiang Shengqiang occasionally gets defeated,
that's just an anomaly.
You're being biased now.
What Jiang Shengqiang did can also be considered
a last-minute change to the battle plan, right?
They both have merit.
But your attitude towards them
is completely different.
I'm not completely dismissing him.
That kid, Guo Zijian,
does have some unorthodox talent.
But
he's hard to manage.
From my years of experience leading troops,
with a personality like his,
sooner or later
he'll cause a major disaster.
What's the situation?
The latest battle report.
Long Yuanshan is targeting our commander
for a decapitation strike.
Our superiors ordered us to return and reinforce immediately.
Staff Officer Hu!
Yes, sir!
Have Li Songwei take a small Battalion Combat Group
and come with me.
Everyone else, return to reinforce immediately!
The command center is in imminent danger.
If you're not returning to reinforce now, where are you going?
Long Yuanshan has already calculated everything.
No matter how many troops we send now, it's useless.
If we want to win this battle,
we must launch a decapitation strike before they do.
Based on satellite and drone target tracking,
locking onto
the Red Army's command center and its security forces.
But note one thing.
Leave Suo Jian'an's command center intact for me.
Flying Eagle copies.
Where... where are they driving to?
Doesn't this road lead to Tiger's Mouth?
Tiger's Mouth?
Yeah.
He lied to me again.
Who lied to you?
So?
The expert verified it.
Is the answer correct?
I'm impressed.
I really am impressed.
Tell you what.
I'll submit a report to my superiors.
You can come to our battalion as my chief staff officer.
No need.
I don't think we're suited to work together.
Why aren't we suited?
I think we're quite in tune.
Besides, the future battlefield...
...will rely more on tools and platforms.
It's all linked to information systems.
If you don't go to the front lines...
...how can you keep up...
...with the rushing tide of army transformation?
No rush.
I have plenty of patience.
Dr. Liang.
Think about it carefully.
I might end up Helping the bad guy.
What are you talking about, Staff Officer Liang?
That came out of nowhere.
The Blue Army's helicopter fleet took a heavy blow.
The Red Army did a great job on this strike.
Yeah, I knew the 396th Brigade...
...would never surrender without a fight.
This Jiang Shengqiang...
...really doesn't mess around in battle.
Not only did he reserve anti-aircraft forces...
...he also kept a main force company...
...to prevent a decapitation strike.
Long Yuanshan has been invincible all these years.
This time...
...it's time he suffered a little.
Flying Eagle calling Wild Wolf.
Wild Wolf copies. Go ahead.
The fleet is under attack by ground anti-aircraft missiles.
The Red Army's anti-aircraft interception...
...was expected.
Initiate plan three.
The first formation will approach at ultra-low altitude...
...and guide fire to strike their reserve forces.
The second formation will change course...
...and flank according to plan three.
Please acknowledge.
Flying Eagle copies.
Report! Communications are restored.
Good.
Report! Message from the 2nd Battalion.
They have engaged a Blue Force
attack helicopter formation.
Three Blue Force attack helicopters
and one transport helicopter were shot down.
The remaining attack helicopters
and transport helicopters fled.
Wasn't Long Yuanshan acting so cocky,
trying to launch a decapitation strike on me?
Why did he fly back?
Have we reached the 1st Battalion?
Report!
We are connected.
Commander Guo ordered the 2nd Armored Infantry Company,
an assault gun platoon,
and some anti-air units back to reinforce the brigade HQ.
He is leading the 1st Infantry Company
and other firepower units
to form a small Battalion Combat Group.
They are heading toward Tiger's Mouth.
Tiger's Mouth?
What is he doing at Tiger's Mouth?
Why is he disobeying orders?
Commander Guo assessed
that Tiger's Mouth
is the current location of the Blue Force HQ.
He assessed?
What gives him the right to make that assessment?
Why did he make an unauthorized decision?
Battalion Commander,
is the Blue Force command post
really at Tiger's Mouth?
You don't trust my judgment?
It's not that.
The conclusion about Yellow Stone Ridge
was based on your data analysis
and Wu Dongsheng's on-site intel.
But going for Tiger's Mouth...
I feel it's still a bit risky.
The problem is
we can't conduct on-site recon right now.
And,
I trust Staff Officer Liang's calculations.
To think our main assault battalion
clearly gave this battle such a good start,
only to be pushed into a corner like this.
It's so frustrating!
Never mind.
Let's risk it all.
If we capture the Black Mamba leader alive,
let's see who dares to show off in front of us.
The battle has reached a point
where it's time for Close-quarters combat.
Yeah.
No matter how well we fought earlier,
if we can't finish strong,
it'll all be for nothing.
Looking at the yellow light indicators,
at every key node,
we have our Exercise Controllers
to ensure no brilliant showdown is missed.
That's good.
We'll have plenty to say at the final review.
Yes, yes.
Right.
Sir.
Look over there.
Bring up the feed.
It's time.
Commence operation.
Report!
Speak.
We are under long-range fire!
Our defense forces suffered heavy losses.
How are they using long-range fire?
Aren't they afraid of hitting their own men?
That was a Blue Force feint.
After pretending to retreat,
they lured our forces into
their long-range strike zone.
Report!
What's the situation?
The Blue Force launched a surprise attack.
Command post support units are heavily damaged.
Hasn't the 2nd Battalion entered the defense zone?
The 2nd Battalion has indeed engaged the enemy.
But they fell for a Blue Force decoy
and were hit hard by their long-range fire.
What about the Reconnaissance Battalion?
They mostly have light weapons.
They can't hold out for long.
Please, sirs,
evacuate immediately!
Political Commissar,
relocate immediately.
I'll stay behind.
Chief of Staff,
protect the Political Commissar.
Regroup with Guo Zijian at once.
Remember, if anything happens to me,
the Political Commissar takes command.
Yes, sir.
Jian'an,
you should evacuate first.
I am the chief military commander.
I ought to stay behind
to handle the remaining command duties.
You go first.
I'll be as quick as I can.
Li Songwei!
Here!
Initiate decapitation strike. Capture Long Yuanshan alive.
Yes, sir!
Teams Two and Seven, move out!
Secure them!
We finally meet.
Deputy Brigade Commander Suo.
Forgive the offense.
Not at all.
Anyway, even if you capture me,
it doesn't count as a successful decapitation strike.
What?
You handed over command?
The exercise control center has live footage.
So what?
You think just because Kang Baoping escaped,
your Red force can make a comeback?
Is that it?
You know very well
your combat losses are heavier than mine.
Deputy Brigade Commander Suo, based on those words alone,
you completely deserve to be a prisoner today.
You think we're fighting with bayonets?
If this is how you lead troops into battle,
I suggest you go back a few decades.
I don't want to waste my breath on you.
You don't believe me?
Let's wait and see.
Wait and see?
What's left to see?
There's nothing left.
Deputy Brigade Commander Suo, the battle is over.
The battle is over.
It's over.
That's impossible.
Notify the command center.
We're returning to Wild Fox Ridge immediately.
Yes, sir.
There's no need.
Deputy Brigade Commander Suo was captured by Long Yuanshan.
The remaining Red forces are extremely scattered,
and the military command center is completely destroyed.
Although Political Commissar Kang Baoping
is currently trying to regroup with you,
based on the First Battalion's current command system,
there is no way to establish effective command.
So,
the target assessment on our side
was submitted by you?
Yes.
And the order to end the exercise
was also based on your assessment?
Yes.
You mean,
the answer you gave me at first
was bait?
No.
If the answer were bait,
that would show bias.
That's not allowed by the exercise rules.
In fact,
the answer was correct.
It's just that you
Outsmarted oneself.
Just two hours ago,
Long Yuanshan was still here.
But he used a time gap against you.
You
fell into his trap.
But we still have our firepower.
I was just about to tell you.
This area
was just hit by the Blue Force's long-range fire.
Battalion Commander Guo,
you are KIA.
So you're saying,
I, Guo Zijian,
am now the biggest joke of the entire exercise.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Even if I had something to say,
it should be at the exercise debriefing
as a formal statement.
There's no need to explain it to you privately here, is there?
Battalion Commander Guo,
a chief staff officer like me...
would you still take me?
Battalion Commander.
The Brigade Staff ordered us
to return to camp immediately.
All battalion commanders must attend tonight's
expanded Brigade Party Committee meeting.
At 8:00 a.m. tomorrow,
the Group Army will hold at the base control hall
an exercise summary and debriefing meeting.
All officers from participating units must attend.
Guo Zijian,
tell me,
do you think you're so great?
That you're invincible?
Why did you act on your own?
At the most critical moment,
you pulled away the 1st Battalion's main force.
Do you realize that this action
made the entire 396th Brigade a joke?